(Sheldon:)I've been thinking about
Dr. Greene's efforts
(Sheldon:)to make science palatable
for the masses.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah? What about it?
(Sheldon:)That's all. I've just
been thinking about it.
(Sheldon:)Now, I'm thinking
about fractal equations.
(Sheldon:)Now I'm thinking about
(Sheldon:)the origin of the phrase
"train of thought."
(Sheldon:)Now I'm thinking about trains.
(Raj:)Are you listening
to this guy?
(Howard:)Hmm? Oh, I'm sorry.
(Howard:)I was somewhere else.
(Leonard:)Lucky bastard.
(Sheldon:)Now I'm thinking about Jell-O.
(Raj:)So what's up?
(Howard:)It's a Bernadette thing.
(Raj:)Oh, no. I hope
everything's okay.
(Leonard:)Whatever it is,
we're here for you.
(Leonard:)You can tell us anything.
(Raj:)Yeah. Good or
devastating.